<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">TourGuidApp</string>

    <!-- Image Content Description -->
    <string name="alex_flag">The Formal flag of Alex city</string>
    <string name="alex_main_image">A picture for famous places in Alexandria</string>
    <string name="image">Image Describes the location</string>


    <!-- Bio of Alexandria City to be Used in History Fragment -->
    <string name="alex_title">Alexandria City</string>
    <string name="alex_bio_1">Alexandria is the second-largest city in Egypt and a major economic center.
        With a population of 5,200,000, Alexandria is the largest city on the Mediterranean, the sixth-largest
        city in the Arab world and the ninth-largest in Africa. The city extends about 40 km (25 mi) at the
        northern coast of Egypt along the Mediterranean Sea. Alexandria is a popular tourist destination, and
        also an important industrial center because of its natural gas and oil pipelines from Suez.</string>
    <string name="alex_bio_2">Alexandria was founded in c. 331 BC by Alexander the Great king of Macedon
        and leader of the Greek League of Corinth, during his conquest of the Achaemenid Empire. An Egyptian
        village named Rhacotis existed at the location and grew into the Egyptian quarter of Alexandria.
        Alexandria grew rapidly to become an important center of Hellenistic civilization and remained the
        capital of Ptolemaic Egypt and Roman and Byzantine Egypt for almost 1,000 years, until the Muslim conquest
        of Egypt in AD 641, when a new capital was founded at Fustat (later absorbed into Cairo). Hellenistic
        Alexandria was best known for the Lighthouse of Alexandria (Pharos), one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient
        World; its Great Library (the largest in the ancient world); and the Necropolis, one of the Seven Wonders
        of the Middle Ages. Alexandria was the intellectual and cultural center of the ancient Mediterranean world
        for much of the Hellenistic age and late antiquity.[4] It was at one time the largest city in the ancient
        world before being eventually overtaken by Rome.</string>


    <!-- First Category Hotel and Restaurant -->
    <!-- First Category titles (hotel_title) -->
    <string name="hotel_title_01">Sheraton Montazah</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_02">Helnan Palestine Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_03">Paradise Inn Beach Resort</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_04">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_05">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_06">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_07">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_08">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_09">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_title_10">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <!-- First Category Bio (hotel_bio) -->
    <string name="hotel_Bio_01">Moderate quarters in a choice business lodging with 3 chic Restaurants, a Night club and
        See-View Pool.</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_02">Polished quarters in an upmarket hotel offering a Private Beach, a Bar and 6 Restaurants.</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_03">Bright beach venue with understated rooms offering Free BreakFast, an Open Air Restaurant
        and 2 Pools.</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_04">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_05">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_06">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_07">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_08">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_09">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <string name="hotel_Bio_10">HOTEL AND RESTAURANT</string>
    <!-- First Category Phone (hotel_phone) -->
    <string name="hotel_Phone_01">+20 35480550</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_02">+20 35473500</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_03">+20 35650152</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_04">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_05">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_06">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_07">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_08">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_09">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="hotel_Phone_10">+20 123456789</string>
    <!-- First Category Maps  (hotel_maps) -->
    <string name="hotel_Maps_01">31.281246,30.011491</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_02">31.288775,30.018072</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_03">31.288932,30.024738</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_04">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_05">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_06">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_07">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_08">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_09">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="hotel_Maps_10">31.18,29.925</string>


    <!-- Second Category Historical places -->
    <!-- Second Category titles (h_title) -->
    <string name="h_title_01">Citadel of Qaitbay</string>
    <string name="h_title_02">Saint Mark\'s Coptic Orthodox Cathedral</string>
    <string name="h_title_03">Caesareum of Alexandria</string>
    <string name="h_title_04">Ras el-Tin Palace</string>
    <string name="h_title_05">Pompey\'s Pillar</string>
    <string name="h_title_06">Abu Al-Abbas Al-Mursi Mosque</string>
    <!-- Second Category Bio (h_bio) -->
    <string name="h_Bio_01">The Citadel of Qaitbay is a 15th-century defensive fortress located on the Mediterranean sea coast,
        in Alexandria,Egypt. It was established in 1477 AD by Sultan Al-Ashraf Sayf al-Din Qait Bay. The Citadel is situated on
        the eastern side of the northern tip of Pharos Island at the mouth of the Eastern Harbour.</string>
    <string name="h_Bio_02">Saint Mark\'s Coptic Orthodox Cathedral is a Coptic church in Alexandria, Egypt. It is the historical
        seat of the Pope of Alexandria, the head of the Coptic Orthodox Church. On Palm Sunday, 9 April 2017, an Islamic State
        operative detonated his suicide belt in the cathedral, killing 17 people and wounding 48.</string>
    <string name="h_Bio_03">The Caesareum of Alexandria is an ancient temple in Alexandria, Egypt. It was conceived by Cleopatra
        VII of the Ptolemaic kingdom, the last pharaoh of Ancient Egypt, to honour her first known lover Julius Caesar. The
        edifice was finished by the Roman Emperor Augustus, after he defeated Mark Antony and Cleopatra in Egypt. He destroyed
        all traces of Antony in Alexandria, and apparently dedicated the temple to his own cult. Converted to a Christian church
        in the late 4th century, the Caesareum was the headquarters of Cyril of Alexandria, the Patriarch of Alexandria from 412
        to 444. The philosopher and mathematician Hypatia was murdered at the Caesareum by a Christian mob in 415; they stripped
        her naked and tore her to pieces. Elements of the temple survived until the 19th century. Cleopatra\'s Needles, obelisks
        from the temple, now stand in Central Park in New York City and on the Thames Embankment, in London;. Today, a large
        statue of the Alexandrine nationalist leader Saad Zaghloul stands on the Caesareum site.</string>
    <string name="h_Bio_04">Ras El Tin Palace is a palace on the coast of the Mediterranean Sea in Alexandria, Egypt. It is one
        of the official residences for a serving President of Egypt. Under the Muhammad Ali Dynasty of Egypt and Sudan, it was
        a royal palace. Ras El Tin Palace is the oldest royal Egyptian palace still in use.</string>
    <string name="h_Bio_05">Pompey\'s Pillar is the name given to a Roman triumphal column in Alexandria, Egypt. Set up in
        honourof the augustus Diocletian between 298-302 AD, the giant Corinthian column originally supported a colossal
        porphyry statue of the emperor in armour. It stands at the eastern side of the temenos of the Serapeum of Alexandria,
        beside the ruins of the temple of Serapis itself. The erroneous name and association with Pompey stems from historical
        misreading of the Greek dedicatory inscription on the base</string>
    <string name="h_Bio_06">The Abu al-Abbas al-Mursi Mosque is an Egyptian mosque in the city of Alexandria. It is dedicated
        to the 13th century Murcian Andalusi Sufi saint Abul Abbas al-Mursi, whose tomb it contains. It is located in the
        Anfoushi neighborhood of Alexandria, near the Citadel of Qaitbay.</string>
    <!-- First Category Maps (h_maps) -->
    <string name="h_Maps_01">31.214059,29.885636</string>
    <string name="h_Maps_02">31.198020,29.899315</string>
    <string name="h_Maps_03">31.200927,29.899401</string>
    <string name="h_Maps_04">31.199207,29.868639</string>
    <string name="h_Maps_05">31.782366,29.896301</string>
    <string name="h_Maps_06">31.205708,29.882384</string>


    <!-- Third Category museums -->
    <!-- Third Category titles (m_) -->
    <string name="_title_01">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_02">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_03">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_04">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_05">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_06">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_07">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_08">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_09">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_title_10">Monuments</string>
    <!-- Third Category Bio (m_) -->
    <string name="_Bio_01">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_02">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_03">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_04">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_05">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_06">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_07">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_08">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_09">Monuments</string>
    <string name="_Bio_10">Monuments</string>
    <!-- Third Category Phone (m_) -->
    <string name="_Phone_01">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_02">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_03">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_04">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_05">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_06">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_07">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_08">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_09">+20 123456789</string>
    <string name="_Phone_10">+20 123456789</string>
    <!-- First Category Maps (m_) -->
    <string name="_Maps_01">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_02">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_03">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_04">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_05">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_06">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_07">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_08">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_09">31.18,29.925</string>
    <string name="_Maps_10">31.18,29.925</string>

</resources>
